{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993607725","data":{"timestamp":" 946993607725"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a68cde73-8527-480c-b582-501dec884a7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993619034","data":{"timestamp":" 946993619034"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a6acfd32-9757-4a1c-84ab-e5d5485d9083"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993619042","data":{"timestamp":" 946993619042"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a6acfd32-9757-4a1c-84ab-e5d5485d9083"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993620704","data":{"timestamp":" 946993620703"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a6acfd32-9757-4a1c-84ab-e5d5485d9083"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993635702","data":{"timestamp":" 946993635702"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a6acfd32-9757-4a1c-84ab-e5d5485d9083"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993646139","data":{"timestamp":" 946993646139"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993646690","data":{"timestamp":" 946993646689"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993647685","data":{"timestamp":" 946993647684"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993648265","data":{"timestamp":" 946993648264"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993648985","data":{"timestamp":" 946993648985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993651657","data":{"timestamp":" 946993651657"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993651940","data":{"timestamp":" 946993651939"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993652613","data":{"timestamp":" 946993652613"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993653195","data":{"timestamp":" 946993653195"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993654053","data":{"timestamp":" 946993654052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993654886","data":{"timestamp":" 946993654886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993655338","data":{"timestamp":" 946993655336"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993656223","data":{"timestamp":" 946993656223"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993657577","data":{"timestamp":" 946993657577"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993658819","data":{"timestamp":" 946993658818"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993658842","data":{"timestamp":" 946993658842"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993659288","data":{"timestamp":" 946993659287"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993659872","data":{"timestamp":" 946993659872"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993662626","data":{"timestamp":" 946993662626"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993663422","data":{"timestamp":" 946993663422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993664530","data":{"timestamp":" 946993664530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993665165","data":{"timestamp":" 946993665165"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993668247","data":{"timestamp":" 946993668247"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993668530","data":{"timestamp":" 946993668530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993669227","data":{"timestamp":" 946993669226"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993669469","data":{"timestamp":" 946993669468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993669917","data":{"timestamp":" 946993669917"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993670590","data":{"timestamp":" 946993670589"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993671001","data":{"timestamp":" 946993671001"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993671995","data":{"timestamp":" 946993671994"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993673397","data":{"timestamp":" 946993673396"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993673912","data":{"timestamp":" 946993673911"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993675221","data":{"timestamp":" 946993675220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993676061","data":{"timestamp":" 946993676060"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993677021","data":{"timestamp":" 946993677021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993679530","data":{"timestamp":" 946993679529"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993680748","data":{"timestamp":" 946993680748"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993681653","data":{"timestamp":" 946993681653"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993682154","data":{"timestamp":" 946993682153"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993683248","data":{"timestamp":" 946993683247"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993683961","data":{"timestamp":" 946993683960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993686539","data":{"timestamp":" 946993686538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993687316","data":{"timestamp":" 946993687316"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993687526","data":{"timestamp":" 946993687526"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993688120","data":{"timestamp":" 946993688120"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993688984","data":{"timestamp":" 946993688984"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993690143","data":{"timestamp":" 946993690143"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993690706","data":{"timestamp":" 946993690705"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993691788","data":{"timestamp":" 946993691788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWACHA"," userResponse":" ALIMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993692456","data":{"timestamp":" 946993692456"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993693341","data":{"timestamp":" 946993693340"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993694342","data":{"timestamp":" 946993694342"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993695023","data":{"timestamp":" 946993695023"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993695644","data":{"timestamp":" 946993695644"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993696129","data":{"timestamp":" 946993696129"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993696913","data":{"timestamp":" 946993696913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAMA"," userResponse":" KUKAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993697449","data":{"timestamp":" 946993697449"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993697466","data":{"timestamp":" 946993697465"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993700042","data":{"timestamp":" 946993700041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993700317","data":{"timestamp":" 946993700316"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993701124","data":{"timestamp":" 946993701123"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993701783","data":{"timestamp":" 946993701782"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993703119","data":{"timestamp":" 946993703118"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993703877","data":{"timestamp":" 946993703877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993704121","data":{"timestamp":" 946993704120"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993704894","data":{"timestamp":" 946993704894"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993705844","data":{"timestamp":" 946993705843"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993706580","data":{"timestamp":" 946993706580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMA"," userResponse":" PEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993707576","data":{"timestamp":" 946993707576"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993707665","data":{"timestamp":" 946993707665"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993708228","data":{"timestamp":" 946993708228"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993711179","data":{"timestamp":" 946993711178"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993711688","data":{"timestamp":" 946993711687"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993712489","data":{"timestamp":" 946993712489"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993713323","data":{"timestamp":" 946993713323"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBAKI"," userResponse":" ALIBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993714170","data":{"timestamp":" 946993714169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993715548","data":{"timestamp":" 946993715547"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993715803","data":{"timestamp":" 946993715803"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993716632","data":{"timestamp":" 946993716632"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993717355","data":{"timestamp":" 946993717354"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993718011","data":{"timestamp":" 946993718011"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993718676","data":{"timestamp":" 946993718676"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993719350","data":{"timestamp":" 946993719350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993720054","data":{"timestamp":" 946993720054"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993722877","data":{"timestamp":" 946993722877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993724366","data":{"timestamp":" 946993724366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANGEKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993725041","data":{"timestamp":" 946993725041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993725224","data":{"timestamp":" 946993725224"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993725930","data":{"timestamp":" 946993725930"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLEA"," userResponse":" KUMLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993728907","data":{"timestamp":" 946993728906"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993729679","data":{"timestamp":" 946993729679"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993730340","data":{"timestamp":" 946993730339"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993730569","data":{"timestamp":" 946993730568"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993731230","data":{"timestamp":" 946993731229"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993732541","data":{"timestamp":" 946993732541"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIPATIKANA"," userResponse":" KILIPATIKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993733220","data":{"timestamp":" 946993733220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKIWA"," userResponse":" KIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993733834","data":{"timestamp":" 946993733834"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993736759","data":{"timestamp":" 946993736759"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993737891","data":{"timestamp":" 946993737891"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILISHANGAZA"," userResponse":" ILISHANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993738828","data":{"timestamp":" 946993738828"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993741915","data":{"timestamp":" 946993741915"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993742715","data":{"timestamp":" 946993742715"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993743558","data":{"timestamp":" 946993743558"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993744825","data":{"timestamp":" 946993744825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEJUA"," userResponse":" ALIYEJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993745457","data":{"timestamp":" 946993745456"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993746501","data":{"timestamp":" 946993746500"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993747208","data":{"timestamp":" 946993747207"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993750636","data":{"timestamp":" 946993750635"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993751178","data":{"timestamp":" 946993751177"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993752532","data":{"timestamp":" 946993752531"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWARIFU"," userResponse":" ALIMWARIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993753183","data":{"timestamp":" 946993753183"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993754126","data":{"timestamp":" 946993754126"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUKIO"," userResponse":" MATUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993754692","data":{"timestamp":" 946993754692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993757419","data":{"timestamp":" 946993757419"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993758281","data":{"timestamp":" 946993758281"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" AKAAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993759583","data":{"timestamp":" 946993759583"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPELELEZA"," userResponse":" KUPELELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993760493","data":{"timestamp":" 946993760493"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993761168","data":{"timestamp":" 946993761167"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APATE"," userResponse":" APATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993761956","data":{"timestamp":" 946993761955"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" UKWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993762841","data":{"timestamp":" 946993762840"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMILI"," userResponse":" KAMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993765871","data":{"timestamp":" 946993765871"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993766555","data":{"timestamp":" 946993766554"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993767717","data":{"timestamp":" 946993767717"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993768440","data":{"timestamp":" 946993768440"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993768524","data":{"timestamp":" 946993768524"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993769186","data":{"timestamp":" 946993769186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993769749","data":{"timestamp":" 946993769749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993770973","data":{"timestamp":" 946993770973"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHANGAA"," userResponse":" AKASHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993771617","data":{"timestamp":" 946993771616"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993772369","data":{"timestamp":" 946993772369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993773134","data":{"timestamp":" 946993773134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINYWA"," userResponse":" AKINYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993773368","data":{"timestamp":" 946993773368"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993774253","data":{"timestamp":" 946993774252"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMALIZA"," userResponse":" KUMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993774947","data":{"timestamp":" 946993774947"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993777755","data":{"timestamp":" 946993777754"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993778316","data":{"timestamp":" 946993778316"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993778576","data":{"timestamp":" 946993778576"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993779823","data":{"timestamp":" 946993779823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHANGAZA"," userResponse":" KUSHANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993782731","data":{"timestamp":" 946993782730"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993782998","data":{"timestamp":" 946993782998"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993783734","data":{"timestamp":" 946993783733"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993784978","data":{"timestamp":" 946993784977"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" WALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993785671","data":{"timestamp":" 946993785670"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993787193","data":{"timestamp":" 946993787193"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993788049","data":{"timestamp":" 946993788048"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993788729","data":{"timestamp":" 946993788728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993789240","data":{"timestamp":" 946993789240"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993790031","data":{"timestamp":" 946993790030"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALALE"," userResponse":" ALALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993790986","data":{"timestamp":" 946993790986"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993791750","data":{"timestamp":" 946993791749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAHAME"," userResponse":" WAHAME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993792376","data":{"timestamp":" 946993792375"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993792924","data":{"timestamp":" 946993792923"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993793577","data":{"timestamp":" 946993793577"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993793802","data":{"timestamp":" 946993793802"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993794486","data":{"timestamp":" 946993794486"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993797347","data":{"timestamp":" 946993797347"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993797981","data":{"timestamp":" 946993797980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993798993","data":{"timestamp":" 946993798992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993799844","data":{"timestamp":" 946993799844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993800075","data":{"timestamp":" 946993800075"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993800750","data":{"timestamp":" 946993800749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993801317","data":{"timestamp":" 946993801317"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993804500","data":{"timestamp":" 946993804499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWACHIA"," userResponse":" WALIMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993805318","data":{"timestamp":" 946993805318"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993805332","data":{"timestamp":" 946993805332"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993806667","data":{"timestamp":" 946993806667"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993807118","data":{"timestamp":" 946993807118"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993807916","data":{"timestamp":" 946993807916"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993811037","data":{"timestamp":" 946993811037"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993811402","data":{"timestamp":" 946993811402"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993812855","data":{"timestamp":" 946993812855"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993814786","data":{"timestamp":" 946993814786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUTA"," userResponse":" AKAKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993815532","data":{"timestamp":" 946993815531"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993817015","data":{"timestamp":" 946993817015"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOACHIWA"," userResponse":" ALIOACHIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993817248","data":{"timestamp":" 946993817248"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993818263","data":{"timestamp":" 946993818263"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" MAZINGIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993818327","data":{"timestamp":" 946993818327"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993819390","data":{"timestamp":" 946993819389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993820347","data":{"timestamp":" 946993820347"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKIWA"," userResponse":" YAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993821124","data":{"timestamp":" 946993821124"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVU"," userResponse":" TULIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993821647","data":{"timestamp":" 946993821647"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993825297","data":{"timestamp":" 946993825297"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993825901","data":{"timestamp":" 946993825900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993826884","data":{"timestamp":" 946993826883"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" AKAAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993827967","data":{"timestamp":" 946993827967"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAUA"," userResponse":" KUWAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993828390","data":{"timestamp":" 946993828389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993829272","data":{"timestamp":" 946993829272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993830526","data":{"timestamp":" 946993830526"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993831000","data":{"timestamp":" 946993831000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993831007","data":{"timestamp":" 946993831007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993833758","data":{"timestamp":" 946993833757"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993834561","data":{"timestamp":" 946993834561"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993834824","data":{"timestamp":" 946993834823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993835378","data":{"timestamp":" 946993835378"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993835400","data":{"timestamp":" 946993835400"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993838436","data":{"timestamp":" 946993838436"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993838450","data":{"timestamp":" 946993838450"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993839564","data":{"timestamp":" 946993839563"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993840798","data":{"timestamp":" 946993840798"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993842020","data":{"timestamp":" 946993842020"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993842764","data":{"timestamp":" 946993842764"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" FULANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993843809","data":{"timestamp":" 946993843809"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPITA"," userResponse":" AKAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993844505","data":{"timestamp":" 946993844504"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993845291","data":{"timestamp":" 946993845290"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993845766","data":{"timestamp":" 946993845766"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993845778","data":{"timestamp":" 946993845778"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993846392","data":{"timestamp":" 946993846392"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993847379","data":{"timestamp":" 946993847379"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993849213","data":{"timestamp":" 946993849213"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMCHINJA"," userResponse":" NITAMCHINJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993849726","data":{"timestamp":" 946993849726"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993849737","data":{"timestamp":" 946993849737"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993850190","data":{"timestamp":" 946993850190"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993850854","data":{"timestamp":" 946993850854"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPATE"," userResponse":" NIPATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993851738","data":{"timestamp":" 946993851738"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITOWEO"," userResponse":" KITOWEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993854685","data":{"timestamp":" 946993854685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMCHOMA"," userResponse":" AKAMCHOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993854968","data":{"timestamp":" 946993854967"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993855661","data":{"timestamp":" 946993855661"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUKI"," userResponse":" MKUKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993856384","data":{"timestamp":" 946993856384"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFA"," userResponse":" AKAFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993859790","data":{"timestamp":" 946993859789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993861033","data":{"timestamp":" 946993861032"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNA"," userResponse":" AKIMCHUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993861816","data":{"timestamp":" 946993861816"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993862919","data":{"timestamp":" 946993862919"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993863713","data":{"timestamp":" 946993863713"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993865049","data":{"timestamp":" 946993865049"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" IKITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993865482","data":{"timestamp":" 946993865482"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993865916","data":{"timestamp":" 946993865916"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993866160","data":{"timestamp":" 946993866159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993866634","data":{"timestamp":" 946993866634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993866641","data":{"timestamp":" 946993866640"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993868694","data":{"timestamp":" 946993868694"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINIUMIZE"," userResponse":" USINIUMIZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993869409","data":{"timestamp":" 946993869409"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993870483","data":{"timestamp":" 946993870483"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993873643","data":{"timestamp":" 946993873643"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993873873","data":{"timestamp":" 946993873872"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993874945","data":{"timestamp":" 946993874944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" KIMIUJIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993876025","data":{"timestamp":" 946993876024"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKA"," userResponse":" AKATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993876623","data":{"timestamp":" 946993876622"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993876892","data":{"timestamp":" 946993876892"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993877483","data":{"timestamp":" 946993877483"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993877501","data":{"timestamp":" 946993877500"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993878266","data":{"timestamp":" 946993878265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993878808","data":{"timestamp":" 946993878808"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993879955","data":{"timestamp":" 946993879954"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJINATA"," userResponse":" KUJINATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993880579","data":{"timestamp":" 946993880578"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993881023","data":{"timestamp":" 946993881022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993881247","data":{"timestamp":" 946993881247"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993882190","data":{"timestamp":" 946993882190"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993882555","data":{"timestamp":" 946993882555"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993885257","data":{"timestamp":" 946993885256"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993886194","data":{"timestamp":" 946993886193"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993886912","data":{"timestamp":" 946993886910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993887860","data":{"timestamp":" 946993887859"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993888465","data":{"timestamp":" 946993888464"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993889224","data":{"timestamp":" 946993889223"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993889707","data":{"timestamp":" 946993889707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993890171","data":{"timestamp":" 946993890171"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993893510","data":{"timestamp":" 946993893510"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993894273","data":{"timestamp":" 946993894273"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993895457","data":{"timestamp":" 946993895457"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHINJIA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHINJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993895970","data":{"timestamp":" 946993895969"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993896554","data":{"timestamp":" 946993896553"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993897185","data":{"timestamp":" 946993897185"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993897377","data":{"timestamp":" 946993897377"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUME"," userResponse":" DUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993899057","data":{"timestamp":" 946993899057"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYENONA"," userResponse":" ALIYENONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993902123","data":{"timestamp":" 946993902122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993902341","data":{"timestamp":" 946993902341"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993903274","data":{"timestamp":" 946993903274"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" KIMIUJIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993904206","data":{"timestamp":" 946993904205"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALA"," userResponse":" AKALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993906007","data":{"timestamp":" 946993906006"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFURAHI"," userResponse":" AKAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993906688","data":{"timestamp":" 946993906688"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993907318","data":{"timestamp":" 946993907318"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993907524","data":{"timestamp":" 946993907524"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993908480","data":{"timestamp":" 946993908479"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993909110","data":{"timestamp":" 946993909109"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993911628","data":{"timestamp":" 946993911626"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993911742","data":{"timestamp":" 946993911741"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993918634","data":{"timestamp":" 946993918634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993925622","data":{"timestamp":" 946993925621"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993931375","data":{"timestamp":" 946993931374"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993945759","data":{"timestamp":" 946993945758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3028913c-3781-4a21-afec-e6ca3bc1387e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993945831","data":{"timestamp":" 946993945831"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8584187f-d324-4403-b4d9-c0bae595b687"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima mwenye rangi ya kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993955024","data":{"timestamp":" 946993955024"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" d0cf9537-c448-4aec-ad8a-b80ad0e3bc0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993956273","data":{"timestamp":" 946993956273"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" d0cf9537-c448-4aec-ad8a-b80ad0e3bc0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993966328","data":{"timestamp":" 946993966328"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a4ba451a-5197-4172-b3aa-c7acbe750863"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993971992","data":{"timestamp":" 946993971992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a4ba451a-5197-4172-b3aa-c7acbe750863"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993976108","data":{"timestamp":" 946993976108"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a4ba451a-5197-4172-b3aa-c7acbe750863"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993989326","data":{"timestamp":" 946993989326"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993995883","data":{"timestamp":" 946993995883"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993997464","data":{"timestamp":" 946993997464"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994001033","data":{"timestamp":" 946994001033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994002642","data":{"timestamp":" 946994002641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GARI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994010546","data":{"timestamp":" 946994010546"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GARI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994012152","data":{"timestamp":" 946994012152"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GIZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994017779","data":{"timestamp":" 946994017779"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GIZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994019341","data":{"timestamp":" 946994019341"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994021896","data":{"timestamp":" 946994021896"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994023477","data":{"timestamp":" 946994023477"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GUNIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994026149","data":{"timestamp":" 946994026148"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GUNIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994027765","data":{"timestamp":" 946994027764"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GAUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994034793","data":{"timestamp":" 946994034793"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GAUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994036408","data":{"timestamp":" 946994036407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GODORO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994041082","data":{"timestamp":" 946994041081"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GODORO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994042640","data":{"timestamp":" 946994042640"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994046709","data":{"timestamp":" 946994046709"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994048718","data":{"timestamp":" 946994048717"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994048823","data":{"timestamp":" 946994048823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994190036","data":{"timestamp":" 946994190036"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 276b97d0-48a0-403c-9974-d12dab858a64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994190103","data":{"timestamp":" 946994190103"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6fd32625-9d95-4130-95a9-f0d8fc898dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994211408","data":{"timestamp":" 946994211407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6fd32625-9d95-4130-95a9-f0d8fc898dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994240066","data":{"timestamp":" 946994240066"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994244922","data":{"timestamp":" 946994244922"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994249448","data":{"timestamp":" 946994249448"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994253858","data":{"timestamp":" 946994253858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994256369","data":{"timestamp":" 946994256369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994256647","data":{"timestamp":" 946994256647"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994260501","data":{"timestamp":" 946994260501"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v8"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994263080","data":{"timestamp":" 946994263080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v8"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994268170","data":{"timestamp":" 946994268169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994273495","data":{"timestamp":" 946994273494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994277913","data":{"timestamp":" 946994277913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994280441","data":{"timestamp":" 946994280441"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994284784","data":{"timestamp":" 946994284784"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994286598","data":{"timestamp":" 946994286598"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994291856","data":{"timestamp":" 946994291856"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994293814","data":{"timestamp":" 946994293812"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 2556e588-0bbe-446c-90d4-b50638cc7c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994313966","data":{"timestamp":" 946994313966"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_R_N"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994320598","data":{"timestamp":" 946994320597"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_W_G"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994327253","data":{"timestamp":" 946994327253"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_E_G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994333914","data":{"timestamp":" 946994333914"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_G_O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994340565","data":{"timestamp":" 946994340565"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_D_G"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994347200","data":{"timestamp":" 946994347199"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_G_U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994353851","data":{"timestamp":" 946994353851"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_G_Y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994360481","data":{"timestamp":" 946994360481"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_W_G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994367102","data":{"timestamp":" 946994367101"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_G_CH"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994373769","data":{"timestamp":" 946994373769"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_G_B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994386946","data":{"timestamp":" 946994386946"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_G_B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040858061","data":{"timestamp":" 947040858060"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f48f7c60-cf7a-4115-94c8-1c0c44192cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_O_G_B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040858122","data":{"timestamp":" 947040858122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3a69bbca-9b7f-41c6-a3d5-37cb7b10414b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040867377","data":{"timestamp":" 947040867377"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 3a69bbca-9b7f-41c6-a3d5-37cb7b10414b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040879308","data":{"timestamp":" 947040879308"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 73153172-1c65-4cc6-9ba0-95d184403c61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040885175","data":{"timestamp":" 947040885174"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 73153172-1c65-4cc6-9ba0-95d184403c61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040890096","data":{"timestamp":" 947040890096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 73153172-1c65-4cc6-9ba0-95d184403c61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040902934","data":{"timestamp":" 947040902933"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b576d9fd-1b6d-4333-8439-131854ad0998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040917878","data":{"timestamp":" 947040917878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b576d9fd-1b6d-4333-8439-131854ad0998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040959007","data":{"timestamp":" 947040959007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040961451","data":{"timestamp":" 947040961451"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040997906","data":{"timestamp":" 947040997906"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041027108","data":{"timestamp":" 947041027108"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041063272","data":{"timestamp":" 947041063271"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041066253","data":{"timestamp":" 947041066253"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041100015","data":{"timestamp":" 947041100014"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041100134","data":{"timestamp":" 947041100133"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6eb361c0-5e82-428c-b9d6-7a4aee097635"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041110148","data":{"timestamp":" 947041110148"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041115025","data":{"timestamp":" 947041115025"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041118879","data":{"timestamp":" 947041118879"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041123065","data":{"timestamp":" 947041123065"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041127376","data":{"timestamp":" 947041127376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041131907","data":{"timestamp":" 947041131907"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041136193","data":{"timestamp":" 947041136192"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041141139","data":{"timestamp":" 947041141138"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041146503","data":{"timestamp":" 947041146503"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041151478","data":{"timestamp":" 947041151478"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041156221","data":{"timestamp":" 947041156221"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041166032","data":{"timestamp":" 947041166031"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041171262","data":{"timestamp":" 947041171262"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041175356","data":{"timestamp":" 947041175356"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041179584","data":{"timestamp":" 947041179584"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041183954","data":{"timestamp":" 947041183954"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041188620","data":{"timestamp":" 947041188620"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041194970","data":{"timestamp":" 947041194970"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041200877","data":{"timestamp":" 947041200877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041209417","data":{"timestamp":" 947041209417"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041217711","data":{"timestamp":" 947041217710"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041223659","data":{"timestamp":" 947041223658"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041229359","data":{"timestamp":" 947041229359"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041233964","data":{"timestamp":" 947041233964"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041238867","data":{"timestamp":" 947041238866"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041244668","data":{"timestamp":" 947041244666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fd58eb8b-c630-4e37-95cb-30ce35a491f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041279069","data":{"timestamp":" 947041279069"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041279899","data":{"timestamp":" 947041279899"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041280563","data":{"timestamp":" 947041280563"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041281303","data":{"timestamp":" 947041281303"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041281789","data":{"timestamp":" 947041281789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041282159","data":{"timestamp":" 947041282159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041286073","data":{"timestamp":" 947041286073"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041286813","data":{"timestamp":" 947041286813"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041289315","data":{"timestamp":" 947041289315"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041289836","data":{"timestamp":" 947041289836"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041290231","data":{"timestamp":" 947041290231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041290634","data":{"timestamp":" 947041290634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041290978","data":{"timestamp":" 947041290978"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041291289","data":{"timestamp":" 947041291289"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041292515","data":{"timestamp":" 947041292515"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041294642","data":{"timestamp":" 947041294641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041294968","data":{"timestamp":" 947041294968"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041295320","data":{"timestamp":" 947041295320"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041295639","data":{"timestamp":" 947041295639"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041296018","data":{"timestamp":" 947041296018"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041296219","data":{"timestamp":" 947041296219"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041297429","data":{"timestamp":" 947041297429"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041297800","data":{"timestamp":" 947041297800"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041298102","data":{"timestamp":" 947041298102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041298875","data":{"timestamp":" 947041298875"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041299202","data":{"timestamp":" 947041299202"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041299521","data":{"timestamp":" 947041299521"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041299857","data":{"timestamp":" 947041299857"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041300042","data":{"timestamp":" 947041300042"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041300303","data":{"timestamp":" 947041300303"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041300613","data":{"timestamp":" 947041300613"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041300899","data":{"timestamp":" 947041300899"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041301151","data":{"timestamp":" 947041301151"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041305485","data":{"timestamp":" 947041305485"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041305779","data":{"timestamp":" 947041305779"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041306106","data":{"timestamp":" 947041306106"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041306392","data":{"timestamp":" 947041306392"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041310407","data":{"timestamp":" 947041310407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041311021","data":{"timestamp":" 947041311021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041311273","data":{"timestamp":" 947041311273"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041311641","data":{"timestamp":" 947041311641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041312767","data":{"timestamp":" 947041312767"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041313078","data":{"timestamp":" 947041313077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041313372","data":{"timestamp":" 947041313372"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041313616","data":{"timestamp":" 947041313616"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041313884","data":{"timestamp":" 947041313884"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041314179","data":{"timestamp":" 947041314178"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041315169","data":{"timestamp":" 947041315169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041317370","data":{"timestamp":" 947041317370"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041317664","data":{"timestamp":" 947041317663"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041317949","data":{"timestamp":" 947041317949"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041318252","data":{"timestamp":" 947041318251"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041318453","data":{"timestamp":" 947041318453"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041322266","data":{"timestamp":" 947041322266"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041324492","data":{"timestamp":" 947041324492"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 8811c8c3-e27c-4c00-896a-cb476c03d65f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041334957","data":{"timestamp":" 947041334957"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041341691","data":{"timestamp":" 947041341690"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041346917","data":{"timestamp":" 947041346917"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041352664","data":{"timestamp":" 947041352664"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041364398","data":{"timestamp":" 947041364398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041381806","data":{"timestamp":" 947041381806"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041387630","data":{"timestamp":" 947041387630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041394156","data":{"timestamp":" 947041394156"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041399205","data":{"timestamp":" 947041399205"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041404170","data":{"timestamp":" 947041404170"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041408519","data":{"timestamp":" 947041408519"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041415138","data":{"timestamp":" 947041415137"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041420919","data":{"timestamp":" 947041420919"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041427807","data":{"timestamp":" 947041427806"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041434361","data":{"timestamp":" 947041434361"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041440159","data":{"timestamp":" 947041440159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041447525","data":{"timestamp":" 947041447525"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041458401","data":{"timestamp":" 947041458401"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041468745","data":{"timestamp":" 947041468745"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041474904","data":{"timestamp":" 947041474904"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041480955","data":{"timestamp":" 947041480955"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041489111","data":{"timestamp":" 947041489110"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041495911","data":{"timestamp":" 947041495910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041502359","data":{"timestamp":" 947041502359"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041511508","data":{"timestamp":" 947041511508"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041518429","data":{"timestamp":" 947041518429"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041560784","data":{"timestamp":" 947041560783"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041566557","data":{"timestamp":" 947041566553"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" f8ddd77d-b427-4c59-8e62-28fbb1e980bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041613671","data":{"timestamp":" 947041613671"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041656809","data":{"timestamp":" 947041656809"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041659313","data":{"timestamp":" 947041659312"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041663724","data":{"timestamp":" 947041663723"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041666547","data":{"timestamp":" 947041666547"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041711564","data":{"timestamp":" 947041711564"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041715076","data":{"timestamp":" 947041715076"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041741221","data":{"timestamp":" 947041741220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041779211","data":{"timestamp":" 947041779211"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041781672","data":{"timestamp":" 947041781672"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041783874","data":{"timestamp":" 947041783873"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041838021","data":{"timestamp":" 947041838016"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041838144","data":{"timestamp":" 947041838144"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAADUI"," userResponse":" MAADUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041846201","data":{"timestamp":" 947041846200"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041853417","data":{"timestamp":" 947041853417"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a01396fd-76f7-4f55-b08f-088c2167277f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041864728","data":{"timestamp":" 947041864727"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041872681","data":{"timestamp":" 947041872681"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041874278","data":{"timestamp":" 947041874277"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041881010","data":{"timestamp":" 947041881010"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041882579","data":{"timestamp":" 947041882579"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041894599","data":{"timestamp":" 947041894598"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041896241","data":{"timestamp":" 947041896241"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041899207","data":{"timestamp":" 947041899207"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041900833","data":{"timestamp":" 947041900833"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041903879","data":{"timestamp":" 947041903879"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041905486","data":{"timestamp":" 947041905485"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041910575","data":{"timestamp":" 947041910574"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041912161","data":{"timestamp":" 947041912161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041914887","data":{"timestamp":" 947041914886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041916516","data":{"timestamp":" 947041916516"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041924777","data":{"timestamp":" 947041924777"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041926351","data":{"timestamp":" 947041926350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041929274","data":{"timestamp":" 947041929274"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041930873","data":{"timestamp":" 947041930872"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041933951","data":{"timestamp":" 947041933951"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041935980","data":{"timestamp":" 947041935979"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041936108","data":{"timestamp":" 947041936108"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b23d40bc-2ceb-40d5-b4a7-8fed55a4e856"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947041982909","data":{"timestamp":" 947041982909"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwake_kwake-tofauti-ajili-hii"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kwake"," userResponse":" kwake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042018002","data":{"timestamp":" 947042018002"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjinga_neno-mjinga-katikati-jimbi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mjinga"," userResponse":" katikati"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042022052","data":{"timestamp":" 947042022052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjinga_neno-mjinga-katikati-jimbi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mjinga"," userResponse":" mjinga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042081838","data":{"timestamp":" 947042081837"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima_nywele-pole-mboga-Kima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Kima"," userResponse":" mboga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042084855","data":{"timestamp":" 947042084854"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima_nywele-pole-mboga-Kima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Kima"," userResponse":" pole"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042087550","data":{"timestamp":" 947042087549"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima_nywele-pole-mboga-Kima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Kima"," userResponse":" nywele"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042090358","data":{"timestamp":" 947042090358"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima_nywele-pole-mboga-Kima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Kima"," userResponse":" Kima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042139550","data":{"timestamp":" 947042139550"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wako_tai-mkia-wako-jirani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" tai"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042142676","data":{"timestamp":" 947042142675"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wako_tai-mkia-wako-jirani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" tai"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042145354","data":{"timestamp":" 947042145354"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wako_tai-mkia-wako-jirani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" tai"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042148255","data":{"timestamp":" 947042148255"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wako_tai-mkia-wako-jirani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" mkia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042150952","data":{"timestamp":" 947042150951"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wako_tai-mkia-wako-jirani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042205179","data":{"timestamp":" 947042205178"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wako_tai-mkia-wako-jirani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042205301","data":{"timestamp":" 947042205301"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAADUI"," userResponse":" MAADUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042215218","data":{"timestamp":" 947042215218"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042229339","data":{"timestamp":" 947042229339"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042237517","data":{"timestamp":" 947042237516"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4c23ac3a-fcff-473d-a8a9-07836e6dd753"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042248375","data":{"timestamp":" 947042248375"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042248618","data":{"timestamp":" 947042248618"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042249513","data":{"timestamp":" 947042249513"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042250012","data":{"timestamp":" 947042250012"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042250606","data":{"timestamp":" 947042250605"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" VYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042251555","data":{"timestamp":" 947042251555"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042252692","data":{"timestamp":" 947042252692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042253591","data":{"timestamp":" 947042253591"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" WANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042254422","data":{"timestamp":" 947042254422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042254706","data":{"timestamp":" 947042254706"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042255501","data":{"timestamp":" 947042255501"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042258112","data":{"timestamp":" 947042258111"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042258310","data":{"timestamp":" 947042258309"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042259158","data":{"timestamp":" 947042259158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" MWITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042260010","data":{"timestamp":" 947042260009"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042260690","data":{"timestamp":" 947042260688"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042261337","data":{"timestamp":" 947042261337"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042261936","data":{"timestamp":" 947042261936"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042263266","data":{"timestamp":" 947042263265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" KUWAOGOFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042266324","data":{"timestamp":" 947042266324"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042266796","data":{"timestamp":" 947042266796"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042267680","data":{"timestamp":" 947042267679"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042268350","data":{"timestamp":" 947042268349"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042268898","data":{"timestamp":" 947042268898"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042269477","data":{"timestamp":" 947042269477"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042271940","data":{"timestamp":" 947042271940"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042273152","data":{"timestamp":" 947042273152"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" WALIWABEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042274203","data":{"timestamp":" 947042274202"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042274432","data":{"timestamp":" 947042274432"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042275561","data":{"timestamp":" 947042275560"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" KUWAONDOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042275967","data":{"timestamp":" 947042275966"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042278985","data":{"timestamp":" 947042278985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042279670","data":{"timestamp":" 947042279670"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042280423","data":{"timestamp":" 947042280423"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" PAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042280639","data":{"timestamp":" 947042280639"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042281342","data":{"timestamp":" 947042281342"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042281967","data":{"timestamp":" 947042281966"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042284623","data":{"timestamp":" 947042284623"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042285416","data":{"timestamp":" 947042285416"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042286340","data":{"timestamp":" 947042286339"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042289480","data":{"timestamp":" 947042289480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042290076","data":{"timestamp":" 947042290076"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042291038","data":{"timestamp":" 947042291037"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042291624","data":{"timestamp":" 947042291623"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" JIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042294767","data":{"timestamp":" 947042294767"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042295559","data":{"timestamp":" 947042295558"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIGUMU"," userResponse":" VIGUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042296260","data":{"timestamp":" 947042296260"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" KUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042297096","data":{"timestamp":" 947042297096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042298259","data":{"timestamp":" 947042298259"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042301260","data":{"timestamp":" 947042301260"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" VICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042302176","data":{"timestamp":" 947042302175"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIMEA"," userResponse":" VILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042303261","data":{"timestamp":" 947042303261"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042303585","data":{"timestamp":" 947042303584"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042304227","data":{"timestamp":" 947042304224"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGO"," userResponse":" PENGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042304511","data":{"timestamp":" 947042304510"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042305319","data":{"timestamp":" 947042305319"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042307878","data":{"timestamp":" 947042307876"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042308701","data":{"timestamp":" 947042308700"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMEA"," userResponse":" ILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042309208","data":{"timestamp":" 947042309208"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042310393","data":{"timestamp":" 947042310392"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITELEMKO"," userResponse":" MITELEMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042310639","data":{"timestamp":" 947042310638"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042311461","data":{"timestamp":" 947042311461"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042314195","data":{"timestamp":" 947042314193"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042315258","data":{"timestamp":" 947042315258"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEGA"," userResponse":" WALITEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042316171","data":{"timestamp":" 947042316170"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042316332","data":{"timestamp":" 947042316332"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042317361","data":{"timestamp":" 947042317361"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBANI"," userResponse":" MIAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042320320","data":{"timestamp":" 947042320320"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042321342","data":{"timestamp":" 947042321342"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" WALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042321959","data":{"timestamp":" 947042321959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042325271","data":{"timestamp":" 947042325271"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042326221","data":{"timestamp":" 947042326221"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042327618","data":{"timestamp":" 947042327617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIONA"," userResponse":" ZILIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042328243","data":{"timestamp":" 947042328243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042329021","data":{"timestamp":" 947042329021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042329276","data":{"timestamp":" 947042329276"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042330159","data":{"timestamp":" 947042330159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042331163","data":{"timestamp":" 947042331162"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOISHI"," userResponse":" ILIVYOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042332357","data":{"timestamp":" 947042332356"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042334883","data":{"timestamp":" 947042334882"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042335109","data":{"timestamp":" 947042335109"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042335603","data":{"timestamp":" 947042335601"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042336475","data":{"timestamp":" 947042336474"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042336687","data":{"timestamp":" 947042336686"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042337800","data":{"timestamp":" 947042337800"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042338680","data":{"timestamp":" 947042338679"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042339667","data":{"timestamp":" 947042339666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042342372","data":{"timestamp":" 947042342371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042342912","data":{"timestamp":" 947042342912"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJE"," userResponse":" MJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042343442","data":{"timestamp":" 947042343441"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042343985","data":{"timestamp":" 947042343985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042346968","data":{"timestamp":" 947042346968"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042347781","data":{"timestamp":" 947042347780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042348768","data":{"timestamp":" 947042348767"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042349560","data":{"timestamp":" 947042349560"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042350720","data":{"timestamp":" 947042350720"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIHAMIA"," userResponse":" ZILIHAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042351778","data":{"timestamp":" 947042351777"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042354220","data":{"timestamp":" 947042354220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042355158","data":{"timestamp":" 947042355156"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042356122","data":{"timestamp":" 947042356122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042356720","data":{"timestamp":" 947042356720"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANGO"," userResponse":" PANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042357424","data":{"timestamp":" 947042357423"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042358218","data":{"timestamp":" 947042358218"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042359049","data":{"timestamp":" 947042359048"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042359529","data":{"timestamp":" 947042359529"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042360510","data":{"timestamp":" 947042360509"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPATA"," userResponse":" WAKAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042361376","data":{"timestamp":" 947042361376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042361540","data":{"timestamp":" 947042361540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042361995","data":{"timestamp":" 947042361994"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042362920","data":{"timestamp":" 947042362918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" SALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042365892","data":{"timestamp":" 947042365892"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042366759","data":{"timestamp":" 947042366758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042367625","data":{"timestamp":" 947042367625"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042368702","data":{"timestamp":" 947042368702"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEPESI"," userResponse":" WEPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042369259","data":{"timestamp":" 947042369258"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042369962","data":{"timestamp":" 947042369959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042370878","data":{"timestamp":" 947042370878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042371500","data":{"timestamp":" 947042371500"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042372445","data":{"timestamp":" 947042372444"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042373285","data":{"timestamp":" 947042373284"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042374151","data":{"timestamp":" 947042374150"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042377820","data":{"timestamp":" 947042377820"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGENING"," userResponse":" WANGENING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042377849","data":{"timestamp":" 947042377849"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042378459","data":{"timestamp":" 947042378459"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042379358","data":{"timestamp":" 947042379358"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042379837","data":{"timestamp":" 947042379836"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042380361","data":{"timestamp":" 947042380361"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042380965","data":{"timestamp":" 947042380965"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042381802","data":{"timestamp":" 947042381801"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFANYA"," userResponse":" HUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042385300","data":{"timestamp":" 947042385300"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042386276","data":{"timestamp":" 947042386275"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042387167","data":{"timestamp":" 947042387167"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIANZA"," userResponse":" VILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042388396","data":{"timestamp":" 947042388394"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBADILIKA"," userResponse":" KUBADILIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042391086","data":{"timestamp":" 947042391086"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042392357","data":{"timestamp":" 947042392357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPUNGUZA"," userResponse":" WALIPUNGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042393391","data":{"timestamp":" 947042393391"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042394038","data":{"timestamp":" 947042394038"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042395075","data":{"timestamp":" 947042395075"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOROMA"," userResponse":" KUKOROMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042395876","data":{"timestamp":" 947042395876"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042398257","data":{"timestamp":" 947042398256"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042398740","data":{"timestamp":" 947042398739"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042399544","data":{"timestamp":" 947042399544"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042400467","data":{"timestamp":" 947042400467"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042401111","data":{"timestamp":" 947042401111"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042402045","data":{"timestamp":" 947042402045"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042402579","data":{"timestamp":" 947042402579"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042403494","data":{"timestamp":" 947042403493"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042404398","data":{"timestamp":" 947042404398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAKUWA"," userResponse":" ZINAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042405342","data":{"timestamp":" 947042405342"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042408260","data":{"timestamp":" 947042408259"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliota nywele zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOTA"," userResponse":" WALIOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042408663","data":{"timestamp":" 947042408663"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliota nywele zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042409613","data":{"timestamp":" 947042409612"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliota nywele zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042412676","data":{"timestamp":" 947042412676"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042414650","data":{"timestamp":" 947042414649"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOANGALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIPOANGALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042416021","data":{"timestamp":" 947042416021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042416617","data":{"timestamp":" 947042416617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042417071","data":{"timestamp":" 947042417071"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042417380","data":{"timestamp":" 947042417379"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042418373","data":{"timestamp":" 947042418373"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042419281","data":{"timestamp":" 947042419281"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAREFU"," userResponse":" MAREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042422483","data":{"timestamp":" 947042422482"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042423566","data":{"timestamp":" 947042423566"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042424322","data":{"timestamp":" 947042424322"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042425203","data":{"timestamp":" 947042425203"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042425984","data":{"timestamp":" 947042425984"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042429568","data":{"timestamp":" 947042429568"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042430505","data":{"timestamp":" 947042430505"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042431386","data":{"timestamp":" 947042431386"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPYA"," userResponse":" VIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042432505","data":{"timestamp":" 947042432505"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAVYO"," userResponse":" AMBAVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042433713","data":{"timestamp":" 947042433713"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042435290","data":{"timestamp":" 947042435289"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042436256","data":{"timestamp":" 947042436255"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEWAHI"," userResponse":" AMEWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042436989","data":{"timestamp":" 947042436989"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042438387","data":{"timestamp":" 947042438387"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042439186","data":{"timestamp":" 947042439186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042440542","data":{"timestamp":" 947042440541"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELENI"," userResponse":" MBELENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042442820","data":{"timestamp":" 947042442820"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiki ndicho kiumbe ambacho watu waliita nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042443348","data":{"timestamp":" 947042443348"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiki ndicho kiumbe ambacho watu waliita nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDICHO"," userResponse":" NDICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042444088","data":{"timestamp":" 947042444088"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiki ndicho kiumbe ambacho watu waliita nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIUMBE"," userResponse":" KIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042445033","data":{"timestamp":" 947042445030"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiki ndicho kiumbe ambacho watu waliita nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBACHO"," userResponse":" AMBACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042445791","data":{"timestamp":" 947042445791"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiki ndicho kiumbe ambacho watu waliita nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042446692","data":{"timestamp":" 947042446691"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiki ndicho kiumbe ambacho watu waliita nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" WALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042447452","data":{"timestamp":" 947042447452"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiki ndicho kiumbe ambacho watu waliita nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042450123","data":{"timestamp":" 947042450122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda nyani waliishi kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042450796","data":{"timestamp":" 947042450795"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda nyani waliishi kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042451652","data":{"timestamp":" 947042451648"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda nyani waliishi kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042452528","data":{"timestamp":" 947042452527"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda nyani waliishi kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042452780","data":{"timestamp":" 947042452779"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda nyani waliishi kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042453566","data":{"timestamp":" 947042453566"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda nyani waliishi kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042456492","data":{"timestamp":" 947042456492"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042457854","data":{"timestamp":" 947042457854"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAKIMBIZA"," userResponse":" KUWAKIMBIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042458672","data":{"timestamp":" 947042458672"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042458880","data":{"timestamp":" 947042458880"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042459812","data":{"timestamp":" 947042459811"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBANI"," userResponse":" MIAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042460690","data":{"timestamp":" 947042460689"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042461383","data":{"timestamp":" 947042461382"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042462146","data":{"timestamp":" 947042462145"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABUU"," userResponse":" MABUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042463389","data":{"timestamp":" 947042463389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliacha kuwakimbiza sungura wa miambani na kula mabuu mchangani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGANI"," userResponse":" MCHANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042467097","data":{"timestamp":" 947042467096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisahau jinsi ya kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISAHAU"," userResponse":" WALISAHAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042467797","data":{"timestamp":" 947042467797"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisahau jinsi ya kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042467920","data":{"timestamp":" 947042467920"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisahau jinsi ya kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042468961","data":{"timestamp":" 947042468960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisahau jinsi ya kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042471776","data":{"timestamp":" 947042471776"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVUA"," userResponse":" WALIVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042472208","data":{"timestamp":" 947042472208"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042472882","data":{"timestamp":" 947042472882"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042473145","data":{"timestamp":" 947042473145"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042473787","data":{"timestamp":" 947042473786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042474411","data":{"timestamp":" 947042474411"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042475008","data":{"timestamp":" 947042475007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042475788","data":{"timestamp":" 947042475785"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042476510","data":{"timestamp":" 947042476509"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042477006","data":{"timestamp":" 947042477004"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042477813","data":{"timestamp":" 947042477813"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042479177","data":{"timestamp":" 947042479176"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNIKWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042479746","data":{"timestamp":" 947042479746"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042480320","data":{"timestamp":" 947042480320"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042481208","data":{"timestamp":" 947042481207"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walivua nguo zao kwa sababu miguu yao na mikono yao ilikuwa imefunikwa kwa nywele nyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUSI"," userResponse":" NYEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042483970","data":{"timestamp":" 947042483970"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bado walikumbuka kwamba walikuwa watu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042485239","data":{"timestamp":" 947042485238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bado walikumbuka kwamba walikuwa watu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042486013","data":{"timestamp":" 947042486013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bado walikumbuka kwamba walikuwa watu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042487296","data":{"timestamp":" 947042487295"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bado walikumbuka kwamba walikuwa watu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042487990","data":{"timestamp":" 947042487990"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bado walikumbuka kwamba walikuwa watu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042491385","data":{"timestamp":" 947042491385"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliangaliana pua zao kubwa na kuchekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANGALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIANGALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042491816","data":{"timestamp":" 947042491816"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliangaliana pua zao kubwa na kuchekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042492310","data":{"timestamp":" 947042492309"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliangaliana pua zao kubwa na kuchekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042493024","data":{"timestamp":" 947042493022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliangaliana pua zao kubwa na kuchekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042493813","data":{"timestamp":" 947042493813"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliangaliana pua zao kubwa na kuchekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042494985","data":{"timestamp":" 947042494984"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliangaliana pua zao kubwa na kuchekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEKANA"," userResponse":" KUCHEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042498622","data":{"timestamp":" 947042498622"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakupenda kule kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042499971","data":{"timestamp":" 947042499970"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakupenda kule kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUPENDA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042500570","data":{"timestamp":" 947042500569"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakupenda kule kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042501521","data":{"timestamp":" 947042501519"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakupenda kule kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEKA"," userResponse":" KUCHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042504503","data":{"timestamp":" 947042504503"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliruka juu na chini kwa hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUKA"," userResponse":" WALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042505153","data":{"timestamp":" 947042505153"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliruka juu na chini kwa hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042505548","data":{"timestamp":" 947042505547"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliruka juu na chini kwa hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042506185","data":{"timestamp":" 947042506184"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliruka juu na chini kwa hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042506470","data":{"timestamp":" 947042506468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliruka juu na chini kwa hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042507289","data":{"timestamp":" 947042507289"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliruka juu na chini kwa hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042510134","data":{"timestamp":" 947042510133"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042510565","data":{"timestamp":" 947042510565"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042511347","data":{"timestamp":" 947042511346"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042511857","data":{"timestamp":" 947042511857"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042512943","data":{"timestamp":" 947042512941"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042513665","data":{"timestamp":" 947042513664"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUISHI"," userResponse":" HUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042514373","data":{"timestamp":" 947042514373"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042515122","data":{"timestamp":" 947042515122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUNDI"," userResponse":" MAKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042515973","data":{"timestamp":" 947042515972"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADOGO"," userResponse":" MADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042516568","data":{"timestamp":" 947042516568"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042517512","data":{"timestamp":" 947042517511"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAISHI"," userResponse":" HAWAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042517986","data":{"timestamp":" 947042517986"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042518693","data":{"timestamp":" 947042518693"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAIFA"," userResponse":" TAIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042518888","data":{"timestamp":" 947042518887"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042519614","data":{"timestamp":" 947042519614"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042522092","data":{"timestamp":" 947042522091"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042522224","data":{"timestamp":" 947042522224"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" a00cb8f6-9f36-46b2-bd14-2be5fd0cbe36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo sababu leo nyani huishi katika makundi madogo na hawaishi kama taifa la nyani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042543173","data":{"timestamp":" 947042543173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_D_W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042549839","data":{"timestamp":" 947042549839"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_L_U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042556553","data":{"timestamp":" 947042556553"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_L_H"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042563222","data":{"timestamp":" 947042563222"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_H_A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042569935","data":{"timestamp":" 947042569934"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_H_G"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042576592","data":{"timestamp":" 947042576591"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_I_J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042583255","data":{"timestamp":" 947042583254"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_N_H"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042589929","data":{"timestamp":" 947042589927"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_U_O"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042596617","data":{"timestamp":" 947042596617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_H_U"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042603353","data":{"timestamp":" 947042603353"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_H_D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042616455","data":{"timestamp":" 947042616454"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" fa4f2756-3ea0-4003-94a5-43d9f04016ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_U_H_D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042627948","data":{"timestamp":" 947042627947"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042637825","data":{"timestamp":" 947042637824"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042644523","data":{"timestamp":" 947042644523"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042649675","data":{"timestamp":" 947042649674"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042655232","data":{"timestamp":" 947042655231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042660005","data":{"timestamp":" 947042660005"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042664484","data":{"timestamp":" 947042664484"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042668730","data":{"timestamp":" 947042668730"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042671788","data":{"timestamp":" 947042671788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042676798","data":{"timestamp":" 947042676797"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042681647","data":{"timestamp":" 947042681647"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042686951","data":{"timestamp":" 947042686951"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042688919","data":{"timestamp":" 947042688918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042695844","data":{"timestamp":" 947042695843"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 6feb4b90-be6a-4a4d-b712-8a2861327767"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042707796","data":{"timestamp":" 947042707796"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042709238","data":{"timestamp":" 947042709238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" UNAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042709780","data":{"timestamp":" 947042709780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042710211","data":{"timestamp":" 947042710209"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042710775","data":{"timestamp":" 947042710775"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042710909","data":{"timestamp":" 947042710908"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042711516","data":{"timestamp":" 947042711516"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042711716","data":{"timestamp":" 947042711715"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042712390","data":{"timestamp":" 947042712389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042714709","data":{"timestamp":" 947042714709"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042715177","data":{"timestamp":" 947042715177"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042715825","data":{"timestamp":" 947042715824"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042716910","data":{"timestamp":" 947042716909"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042717574","data":{"timestamp":" 947042717573"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042718122","data":{"timestamp":" 947042718122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042718821","data":{"timestamp":" 947042718821"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIKI"," userResponse":" MILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042718886","data":{"timestamp":" 947042718886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042719602","data":{"timestamp":" 947042719602"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042720993","data":{"timestamp":" 947042720992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIYEWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042721851","data":{"timestamp":" 947042721851"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042722609","data":{"timestamp":" 947042722609"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042722743","data":{"timestamp":" 947042722743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042723282","data":{"timestamp":" 947042723282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042724584","data":{"timestamp":" 947042724583"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042725077","data":{"timestamp":" 947042725077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILA"," userResponse":" ILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042725698","data":{"timestamp":" 947042725698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042726346","data":{"timestamp":" 947042726346"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042726766","data":{"timestamp":" 947042726766"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042727343","data":{"timestamp":" 947042727343"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042728184","data":{"timestamp":" 947042728184"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPINZANI"," userResponse":" WAPINZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042728615","data":{"timestamp":" 947042728615"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042729266","data":{"timestamp":" 947042729265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042754487","data":{"timestamp":" 947042754486"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042754583","data":{"timestamp":" 947042754583"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042761943","data":{"timestamp":" 947042761942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042771161","data":{"timestamp":" 947042771161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042777677","data":{"timestamp":" 947042777676"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" b9a74d56-6b3f-4846-af1e-a6598aa0552f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042792348","data":{"timestamp":" 947042792348"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042793287","data":{"timestamp":" 947042793286"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042794132","data":{"timestamp":" 947042794132"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042797799","data":{"timestamp":" 947042797799"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042798751","data":{"timestamp":" 947042798751"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042802054","data":{"timestamp":" 947042802054"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LESIBA"," userResponse":" LESIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042803067","data":{"timestamp":" 947042803067"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042806887","data":{"timestamp":" 947042806887"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042807834","data":{"timestamp":" 947042807834"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042810879","data":{"timestamp":" 947042810879"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042811107","data":{"timestamp":" 947042811107"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042811648","data":{"timestamp":" 947042811648"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042812682","data":{"timestamp":" 947042812680"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPIKA"," userResponse":" WANAPIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042815548","data":{"timestamp":" 947042815548"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042817118","data":{"timestamp":" 947042817118"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042820146","data":{"timestamp":" 947042820146"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042820457","data":{"timestamp":" 947042820457"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042821184","data":{"timestamp":" 947042821184"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042822485","data":{"timestamp":" 947042822485"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAREKEBISHA"," userResponse":" WANAREKEBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042823217","data":{"timestamp":" 947042823216"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042826826","data":{"timestamp":" 947042826812"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042827783","data":{"timestamp":" 947042827782"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042830443","data":{"timestamp":" 947042830443"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042831506","data":{"timestamp":" 947042831506"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042831757","data":{"timestamp":" 947042831757"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042833176","data":{"timestamp":" 947042833176"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KUKIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042833904","data":{"timestamp":" 947042833904"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042834529","data":{"timestamp":" 947042834529"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042835337","data":{"timestamp":" 947042835337"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042838001","data":{"timestamp":" 947042837997"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042838113","data":{"timestamp":" 947042838113"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042845158","data":{"timestamp":" 947042845157"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042851101","data":{"timestamp":" 947042851101"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042857414","data":{"timestamp":" 947042857414"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 5d36754a-5794-4343-baf1-98c2a87acb3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042867357","data":{"timestamp":" 947042867357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042868542","data":{"timestamp":" 947042868542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" NINAPOMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042869136","data":{"timestamp":" 947042869136"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042869377","data":{"timestamp":" 947042869376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042869830","data":{"timestamp":" 947042869829"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042870535","data":{"timestamp":" 947042870534"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042871475","data":{"timestamp":" 947042871475"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042873826","data":{"timestamp":" 947042873825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042874357","data":{"timestamp":" 947042874357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042875402","data":{"timestamp":" 947042875402"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042876018","data":{"timestamp":" 947042876018"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042876656","data":{"timestamp":" 947042876655"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042877690","data":{"timestamp":" 947042877689"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042880158","data":{"timestamp":" 947042880158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042881031","data":{"timestamp":" 947042881031"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042881495","data":{"timestamp":" 947042881495"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042882499","data":{"timestamp":" 947042882499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042884995","data":{"timestamp":" 947042884995"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042885980","data":{"timestamp":" 947042885979"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042889138","data":{"timestamp":" 947042889138"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042889621","data":{"timestamp":" 947042889621"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042889725","data":{"timestamp":" 947042889724"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042890429","data":{"timestamp":" 947042890429"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042891395","data":{"timestamp":" 947042891395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042892059","data":{"timestamp":" 947042892059"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042892883","data":{"timestamp":" 947042892883"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042893458","data":{"timestamp":" 947042893458"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042895940","data":{"timestamp":" 947042895937"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042896403","data":{"timestamp":" 947042896403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042896878","data":{"timestamp":" 947042896878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042897665","data":{"timestamp":" 947042897665"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042898260","data":{"timestamp":" 947042898260"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042898945","data":{"timestamp":" 947042898944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042899542","data":{"timestamp":" 947042899542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANYWA"," userResponse":" KUYANYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042902030","data":{"timestamp":" 947042902030"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042902915","data":{"timestamp":" 947042902915"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042903387","data":{"timestamp":" 947042903387"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042904390","data":{"timestamp":" 947042904390"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042906898","data":{"timestamp":" 947042906898"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042907887","data":{"timestamp":" 947042907887"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042911332","data":{"timestamp":" 947042911332"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPAZIA"," userResponse":" MAPAZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042911407","data":{"timestamp":" 947042911406"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042912361","data":{"timestamp":" 947042912361"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADIRISHA"," userResponse":" MADIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042914082","data":{"timestamp":" 947042914082"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" YANAPAPATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042914686","data":{"timestamp":" 947042914685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042915142","data":{"timestamp":" 947042915141"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042915684","data":{"timestamp":" 947042915683"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042917385","data":{"timestamp":" 947042917385"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANANIPANGUSA"," userResponse":" YANANIPANGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042917809","data":{"timestamp":" 947042917809"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042918354","data":{"timestamp":" 947042918353"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042920728","data":{"timestamp":" 947042920728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042921623","data":{"timestamp":" 947042921623"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042922140","data":{"timestamp":" 947042922140"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042923204","data":{"timestamp":" 947042923204"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042925645","data":{"timestamp":" 947042925645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042926630","data":{"timestamp":" 947042926630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042929748","data":{"timestamp":" 947042929748"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042930008","data":{"timestamp":" 947042930008"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042930981","data":{"timestamp":" 947042930980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042933685","data":{"timestamp":" 947042933685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042934477","data":{"timestamp":" 947042934476"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042935673","data":{"timestamp":" 947042935673"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANASONGA"," userResponse":" YANASONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042936273","data":{"timestamp":" 947042936272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042936747","data":{"timestamp":" 947042936747"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042939145","data":{"timestamp":" 947042939144"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042940039","data":{"timestamp":" 947042940037"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042940511","data":{"timestamp":" 947042940511"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042941538","data":{"timestamp":" 947042941538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042944036","data":{"timestamp":" 947042944036"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042945046","data":{"timestamp":" 947042945046"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042948436","data":{"timestamp":" 947042948436"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042949861","data":{"timestamp":" 947042949861"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042950356","data":{"timestamp":" 947042950356"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042951114","data":{"timestamp":" 947042951114"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042952155","data":{"timestamp":" 947042952154"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTETEMEKA"," userResponse":" KUTETEMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042955079","data":{"timestamp":" 947042955079"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042956442","data":{"timestamp":" 947042956442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAANGUKA"," userResponse":" YANAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042956804","data":{"timestamp":" 947042956803"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042957397","data":{"timestamp":" 947042957397"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042960238","data":{"timestamp":" 947042960238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042961232","data":{"timestamp":" 947042961231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042961737","data":{"timestamp":" 947042961736"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042964188","data":{"timestamp":" 947042964188"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042965182","data":{"timestamp":" 947042965181"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042968312","data":{"timestamp":" 947042968311"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042968507","data":{"timestamp":" 947042968507"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042969260","data":{"timestamp":" 947042969260"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042970585","data":{"timestamp":" 947042970584"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUNACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042971910","data":{"timestamp":" 947042971910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042972826","data":{"timestamp":" 947042972825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042973859","data":{"timestamp":" 947042973859"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUSIA"," userResponse":" KUNUSIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042975139","data":{"timestamp":" 947042975139"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042975866","data":{"timestamp":" 947042975866"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAZO"," userResponse":" AMBAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042976389","data":{"timestamp":" 947042976388"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042977632","data":{"timestamp":" 947042977630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" ANATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042979984","data":{"timestamp":" 947042979984"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042980886","data":{"timestamp":" 947042980886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042981396","data":{"timestamp":" 947042981395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042982462","data":{"timestamp":" 947042982461"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042984913","data":{"timestamp":" 947042984913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042985911","data":{"timestamp":" 947042985910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042989254","data":{"timestamp":" 947042989253"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILAURI"," userResponse":" BILAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042989758","data":{"timestamp":" 947042989758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYO"," userResponse":" ILIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042990747","data":{"timestamp":" 947042990747"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042991825","data":{"timestamp":" 947042991825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAANGUKA"," userResponse":" INAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042992296","data":{"timestamp":" 947042992295"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042992495","data":{"timestamp":" 947042992495"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042993309","data":{"timestamp":" 947042993308"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042995860","data":{"timestamp":" 947042995859"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASHUKURU"," userResponse":" NASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042996478","data":{"timestamp":" 947042996478"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUNGU"," userResponse":" MUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042997464","data":{"timestamp":" 947042997464"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042998117","data":{"timestamp":" 947042998117"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043000573","data":{"timestamp":" 947043000572"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043001416","data":{"timestamp":" 947043001416"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043002170","data":{"timestamp":" 947043002170"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATILI"," userResponse":" UKATILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043002584","data":{"timestamp":" 947043002584"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043005066","data":{"timestamp":" 947043005066"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043005580","data":{"timestamp":" 947043005580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043006587","data":{"timestamp":" 947043006587"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043006851","data":{"timestamp":" 947043006851"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043007770","data":{"timestamp":" 947043007770"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043010969","data":{"timestamp":" 947043010968"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIRIMBI"," userResponse":" FIRIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043012113","data":{"timestamp":" 947043012113"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAPULIZWA"," userResponse":" INAPULIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043014381","data":{"timestamp":" 947043014380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043014545","data":{"timestamp":" 947043014545"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043015170","data":{"timestamp":" 947043015169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043016118","data":{"timestamp":" 947043016118"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAINGIA"," userResponse":" LINAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043018919","data":{"timestamp":" 947043018918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SILIONI"," userResponse":" SILIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043019822","data":{"timestamp":" 947043019822"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043020418","data":{"timestamp":" 947043020418"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043020788","data":{"timestamp":" 947043020788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043021318","data":{"timestamp":" 947043021318"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043023852","data":{"timestamp":" 947043023849"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043024742","data":{"timestamp":" 947043024741"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043025214","data":{"timestamp":" 947043025214"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043026218","data":{"timestamp":" 947043026217"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043028743","data":{"timestamp":" 947043028743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043029757","data":{"timestamp":" 947043029756"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043033720","data":{"timestamp":" 947043033720"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haionekani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONEKANI"," userResponse":" HAIONEKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043036864","data":{"timestamp":" 947043036864"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haisikiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAISIKIKI"," userResponse":" HAISIKIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043039427","data":{"timestamp":" 947043039426"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAFANYA"," userResponse":" INAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043039818","data":{"timestamp":" 947043039817"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043040424","data":{"timestamp":" 947043040424"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043041174","data":{"timestamp":" 947043041173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043041624","data":{"timestamp":" 947043041623"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043044217","data":{"timestamp":" 947043044217"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043044648","data":{"timestamp":" 947043044648"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043045456","data":{"timestamp":" 947043045456"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043047971","data":{"timestamp":" 947043047971"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043048718","data":{"timestamp":" 947043048718"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043050920","data":{"timestamp":" 947043050920"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043051682","data":{"timestamp":" 947043051681"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043066941","data":{"timestamp":" 947043066940"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043067039","data":{"timestamp":" 947043067039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043073196","data":{"timestamp":" 947043073195"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043079705","data":{"timestamp":" 947043079703"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043085747","data":{"timestamp":" 947043085747"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 4775d3e3-683b-4f15-8895-145cc1e4648d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043095252","data":{"timestamp":" 947043095251"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043096143","data":{"timestamp":" 947043096143"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043097207","data":{"timestamp":" 947043097207"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043097480","data":{"timestamp":" 947043097480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043098010","data":{"timestamp":" 947043098009"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043098854","data":{"timestamp":" 947043098853"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043101507","data":{"timestamp":" 947043101506"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043102112","data":{"timestamp":" 947043102112"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043102946","data":{"timestamp":" 947043102946"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043103422","data":{"timestamp":" 947043103422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043104103","data":{"timestamp":" 947043104103"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043106944","data":{"timestamp":" 947043106944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043107823","data":{"timestamp":" 947043107822"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043108620","data":{"timestamp":" 947043108618"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043109249","data":{"timestamp":" 947043109248"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043109923","data":{"timestamp":" 947043109923"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043112966","data":{"timestamp":" 947043112965"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043113676","data":{"timestamp":" 947043113676"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043114654","data":{"timestamp":" 947043114654"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043115720","data":{"timestamp":" 947043115720"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEISHI"," userResponse":" ALIYEISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043116367","data":{"timestamp":" 947043116366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043116998","data":{"timestamp":" 947043116997"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043118219","data":{"timestamp":" 947043118218"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043118847","data":{"timestamp":" 947043118847"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043119007","data":{"timestamp":" 947043119007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043119567","data":{"timestamp":" 947043119567"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043120776","data":{"timestamp":" 947043120776"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043122096","data":{"timestamp":" 947043122096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043122618","data":{"timestamp":" 947043122618"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043122969","data":{"timestamp":" 947043122969"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043123926","data":{"timestamp":" 947043123925"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZURI"," userResponse":" KIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043125143","data":{"timestamp":" 947043125143"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043125800","data":{"timestamp":" 947043125800"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043126695","data":{"timestamp":" 947043126695"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEJAA"," userResponse":" UMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043127001","data":{"timestamp":" 947043127001"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANG"," userResponse":" MANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043127516","data":{"timestamp":" 947043127516"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMUNG"," userResponse":" AMUNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043128074","data":{"timestamp":" 947043128074"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMU"," userResponse":" AMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043128900","data":{"timestamp":" 947043128900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043129517","data":{"timestamp":" 947043129517"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043130936","data":{"timestamp":" 947043130935"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIKULOWESHA"," userResponse":" IKIKULOWESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043134039","data":{"timestamp":" 947043134039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043134934","data":{"timestamp":" 947043134934"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043136299","data":{"timestamp":" 947043136299"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNALALA"," userResponse":" TUNALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043137783","data":{"timestamp":" 947043137783"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" FOFOFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043139087","data":{"timestamp":" 947043139087"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043139400","data":{"timestamp":" 947043139400"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043140573","data":{"timestamp":" 947043140573"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATEMI"," userResponse":" WATEMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043143738","data":{"timestamp":" 947043143738"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043144709","data":{"timestamp":" 947043144708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043145838","data":{"timestamp":" 947043145837"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043146379","data":{"timestamp":" 947043146377"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043149400","data":{"timestamp":" 947043149399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFADHALI"," userResponse":" AFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043150552","data":{"timestamp":" 947043150552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNITEMBELEE"," userResponse":" UNITEMBELEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043151393","data":{"timestamp":" 947043151393"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043151981","data":{"timestamp":" 947043151981"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043153193","data":{"timestamp":" 947043153193"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONE"," userResponse":" UKAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043154514","data":{"timestamp":" 947043154513"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAHARI"," userResponse":" FAHARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043156023","data":{"timestamp":" 947043156022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPO"," userResponse":" ILIYOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043156645","data":{"timestamp":" 947043156645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043157727","data":{"timestamp":" 947043157726"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043159153","data":{"timestamp":" 947043159153"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043159731","data":{"timestamp":" 947043159731"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043159908","data":{"timestamp":" 947043159907"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043160544","data":{"timestamp":" 947043160544"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043162943","data":{"timestamp":" 947043162942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043163547","data":{"timestamp":" 947043163547"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043164223","data":{"timestamp":" 947043164223"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043165041","data":{"timestamp":" 947043165041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043166246","data":{"timestamp":" 947043166246"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043166781","data":{"timestamp":" 947043166781"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043166951","data":{"timestamp":" 947043166951"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043167568","data":{"timestamp":" 947043167568"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043169945","data":{"timestamp":" 947043169944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043170705","data":{"timestamp":" 947043170705"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043171227","data":{"timestamp":" 947043171227"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043172062","data":{"timestamp":" 947043172062"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRIJA"," userResponse":" MRIJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043173295","data":{"timestamp":" 947043173295"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" UNAOSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043174376","data":{"timestamp":" 947043174375"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINWAJI"," userResponse":" KINWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043177586","data":{"timestamp":" 947043177586"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043178451","data":{"timestamp":" 947043178451"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043178919","data":{"timestamp":" 947043178918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043179789","data":{"timestamp":" 947043179789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043180322","data":{"timestamp":" 947043180322"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043181742","data":{"timestamp":" 947043181742"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043183050","data":{"timestamp":" 947043183050"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJABU"," userResponse":" AJABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043184333","data":{"timestamp":" 947043184333"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFOKA"," userResponse":" AKIFOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043185170","data":{"timestamp":" 947043185169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUSI"," userResponse":" MATUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043186544","data":{"timestamp":" 947043186544"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043187010","data":{"timestamp":" 947043187010"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043187862","data":{"timestamp":" 947043187862"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOKULA"," userResponse":" WANAOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043188391","data":{"timestamp":" 947043188390"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043188886","data":{"timestamp":" 947043188885"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043190467","data":{"timestamp":" 947043190466"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAONA"," userResponse":" WATAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043190822","data":{"timestamp":" 947043190822"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043191443","data":{"timestamp":" 947043191442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEMA"," userResponse":" MTEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043192322","data":{"timestamp":" 947043192322"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043194680","data":{"timestamp":" 947043194680"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043196140","data":{"timestamp":" 947043196139"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWATEGEA"," userResponse":" AKAWATEGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043196798","data":{"timestamp":" 947043196798"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043197897","data":{"timestamp":" 947043197897"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ULIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043199127","data":{"timestamp":" 947043199127"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043202140","data":{"timestamp":" 947043202140"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043203101","data":{"timestamp":" 947043203101"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" WALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043203927","data":{"timestamp":" 947043203927"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043204368","data":{"timestamp":" 947043204368"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043205168","data":{"timestamp":" 947043205168"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043206060","data":{"timestamp":" 947043206060"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOMO"," userResponse":" VILIVYOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043208921","data":{"timestamp":" 947043208921"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" WALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043209976","data":{"timestamp":" 947043209976"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEKA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043210821","data":{"timestamp":" 947043210820"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHU"," userResponse":" CHU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043215546","data":{"timestamp":" 947043215546"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOUFIKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPOUFIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043216242","data":{"timestamp":" 947043216242"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043217092","data":{"timestamp":" 947043217092"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043217281","data":{"timestamp":" 947043217280"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043217807","data":{"timestamp":" 947043217807"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043218793","data":{"timestamp":" 947043218793"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043220096","data":{"timestamp":" 947043220095"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" WACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043220849","data":{"timestamp":" 947043220849"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIONJE"," userResponse":" NIONJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043221663","data":{"timestamp":" 947043221663"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043224750","data":{"timestamp":" 947043224750"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAZAMA"," userResponse":" TAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043225422","data":{"timestamp":" 947043225422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043226085","data":{"timestamp":" 947043226085"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043227049","data":{"timestamp":" 947043227049"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAVYOKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAVYOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043227523","data":{"timestamp":" 947043227523"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043230607","data":{"timestamp":" 947043230606"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043231209","data":{"timestamp":" 947043231209"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043231786","data":{"timestamp":" 947043231786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043232522","data":{"timestamp":" 947043232522"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAPATA"," userResponse":" HAJAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043233169","data":{"timestamp":" 947043233169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUGUSA"," userResponse":" KUGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043234427","data":{"timestamp":" 947043234427"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043235603","data":{"timestamp":" 947043235603"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043237089","data":{"timestamp":" 947043237088"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAMNASA"," userResponse":" UKAMNASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043237712","data":{"timestamp":" 947043237710"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043240369","data":{"timestamp":" 947043240369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043241026","data":{"timestamp":" 947043241026"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043242728","data":{"timestamp":" 947043242727"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKABUBUJIKA"," userResponse":" YAKABUBUJIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043243261","data":{"timestamp":" 947043243260"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043244406","data":{"timestamp":" 947043244405"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILINGANYI"," userResponse":" MBILINGANYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043247353","data":{"timestamp":" 947043247353"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043247540","data":{"timestamp":" 947043247540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043248085","data":{"timestamp":" 947043248085"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043249508","data":{"timestamp":" 947043249508"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMTAZAMA"," userResponse":" AKAMTAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043251141","data":{"timestamp":" 947043251141"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEDUWAA"," userResponse":" AMEDUWAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043254091","data":{"timestamp":" 947043254091"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043254824","data":{"timestamp":" 947043254824"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043257237","data":{"timestamp":" 947043257237"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEEE"," userResponse":" HEEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043259122","data":{"timestamp":" 947043259121"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043259596","data":{"timestamp":" 947043259596"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043260280","data":{"timestamp":" 947043260280"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMU"," userResponse":" KITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043260613","data":{"timestamp":" 947043260613"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043261869","data":{"timestamp":" 947043261869"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULICHOKULA"," userResponse":" ULICHOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043263591","data":{"timestamp":" 947043263590"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKAYAFANYA"," userResponse":" KIKAYAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043264189","data":{"timestamp":" 947043264189"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043265187","data":{"timestamp":" 947043265186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YABUBUJIKE"," userResponse":" YABUBUJIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043268627","data":{"timestamp":" 947043268626"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043269216","data":{"timestamp":" 947043269215"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043269393","data":{"timestamp":" 947043269393"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043269948","data":{"timestamp":" 947043269948"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043270979","data":{"timestamp":" 947043270979"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHINDWA"," userResponse":" AKASHINDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043271709","data":{"timestamp":" 947043271708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIBU"," userResponse":" KUJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043274697","data":{"timestamp":" 947043274697"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043274841","data":{"timestamp":" 947043274841"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043275349","data":{"timestamp":" 947043275349"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043276563","data":{"timestamp":" 947043276563"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" AKAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043277563","data":{"timestamp":" 947043277563"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKEJELI"," userResponse":" AKIKEJELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043278759","data":{"timestamp":" 947043278758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DU"," userResponse":" DU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043281443","data":{"timestamp":" 947043281443"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEKULA"," userResponse":" UMEKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043282139","data":{"timestamp":" 947043282139"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043282687","data":{"timestamp":" 947043282687"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIASI"," userResponse":" KIASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043283879","data":{"timestamp":" 947043283879"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIVIWEZI"," userResponse":" SIVIWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043284618","data":{"timestamp":" 947043284617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043285284","data":{"timestamp":" 947043285283"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043287146","data":{"timestamp":" 947043287145"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVYOHIMIDI"," userResponse":" UNAVYOHIMIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043291677","data":{"timestamp":" 947043291676"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEPO"," userResponse":" KUWEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043292422","data":{"timestamp":" 947043292422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043293105","data":{"timestamp":" 947043293105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNAKO"," userResponse":" KUNAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043293942","data":{"timestamp":" 947043293942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKAA"," userResponse":" CHAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043294908","data":{"timestamp":" 947043294907"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRADI"," userResponse":" MRADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043295660","data":{"timestamp":" 947043295660"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKO"," userResponse":" KWAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043296276","data":{"timestamp":" 947043296276"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043296764","data":{"timestamp":" 947043296764"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BORA"," userResponse":" BORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043297502","data":{"timestamp":" 947043297502"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043298198","data":{"timestamp":" 947043298198"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEPO"," userResponse":" KUWEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043298912","data":{"timestamp":" 947043298912"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043299628","data":{"timestamp":" 947043299628"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZURI"," userResponse":" KUZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043300351","data":{"timestamp":" 947043300350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043301797","data":{"timestamp":" 947043301797"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGALAU"," userResponse":" ANGALAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043301997","data":{"timestamp":" 947043301997"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043302482","data":{"timestamp":" 947043302482"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043302683","data":{"timestamp":" 947043302682"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043303492","data":{"timestamp":" 947043303491"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043304007","data":{"timestamp":" 947043304005"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043306471","data":{"timestamp":" 947043306468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043306655","data":{"timestamp":" 947043306655"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_164637"," gameId":" 9fd73b6b-cf73-4d08-b341-5636acb90911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}